Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Court urges arbitration in fur dispute, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: Dressers, dyers ask 10% wage cut, union requests 10 to 20% increase, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Dressers, dyers hold further wage talks, Decision on Potash trial date pending, 1950-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: Employer-Union fur litigation motions filed, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Endicott is denied plea, 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Endicott takes case to Supreme Court, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: Firms warn of tannery strike effects, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: Forced to bow to closed shop, fur men assert, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 43: Full-fashioned hose workers to ask raise, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: Fulton Tanners reject parleys with union, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: Fur dressers guild signs new labor contract, work resume, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: Fur dressers make revised wage offer, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 47: Fur field held 98% unionized, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: Fur industry carries on without union agreement, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: Fur industry votes Tuesday on shutdown, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 50: Fur industry votes Tuesday on shutdown, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: Fur men testify they are forced to accept closed shop, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Fur parleys stalemated, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 53: Fur pattern workers win wage increase, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 54: Fur strike set April 26 unless lockout halts, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 55: Fur union agrees to an 11% pay-cut, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 56: Fur union agrees to reduction in staff to keep large warehouse from closing, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 57: Hold Gloversville Fur Strike vote tomorrow, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 58: Leather plant boosts wages, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 59: 17 Tanneries may reopen without union, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 60: 8,000 workers begin strike in fur industry, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 61: A. Hollander & Son Employees get $300,000 wage increase, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 62: Accord is set, Fur workers to return Monday, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 63: AFL to oppose fur union group, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 64: Anti-Red fur men get CIO ovation, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 65: Appellate division rules associated fur must arbitrate strike damage action, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 66: Associated fur must arbitrate labor dispute, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 67: Basch concern signs contract ending dispute, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 68: Ben Gold to surrender, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 69: Union must share blame for present dispute..., 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 70: Union pickets as shop drops alteration dept., 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 71: Union plans mass meeting Friday to air negotiations, 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 72: Union rejects AFM demand for wage cut, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 73: Union rejects bid to legalize contracting, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 74: Fur union board scores CIO chiefs, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 75: Fur union moves to AFL merger, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 76: Fur union ousts 11 officers here, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 77: Fur union quits CIO to escape 'Red' trial, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 78: Fur union reelects Potash as manager, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 79: Fur union Schism widens, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 80: Fur union shifts AFL entry plan, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 81: Fur union to accept non-Communist oath, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 82: Fur union's buses raked by missiles, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 83: Fur workers act to revive 3-year pact, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 84: Fur workers return Monday, union agrees to 2-price plan, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 85: Fur workers walk out of 30 plants here, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 86: Fur, Parleys Fail, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 87: Furriers merge in spite of AFL, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 88: Glove lining shops strike ended by raise, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 89: Gloversville Tannery dispute at impasse, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 90: Gold warns union of 'difficulties', 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 91: Guild contract still unsettled.., 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 92: Guild workers get new pay increases effective this week, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 93: Hear guild presents pact counter demands, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 94: Hear stoppage in fur plants will halt today, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 95: Hollander and union reach agreement, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 96: Industry shutdown of 2 months or more..., 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 97: Irving Potash held for deportation, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 98: Labor troubles lead to breakup of Southern California Retail Guild, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 99: Labor-Mfrs. Confer again on contract, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 100: Labor-Mft. clash seen by Union in Potash arrest, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 101: Leather men avoid strike in bay state, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 102: Leather supply near exhaustion, firms in Gloversville say, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 103: Meet today to avert strike of Tanners, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 104: Mfrs. Announce demands, union meeting postponed, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 105: More witnesses tell about union's industry activity, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 106: New England Tanners Union agree on pact, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 107: New England Union shows effect of anti-Red code, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 108: New fur labor pact being negotiated in Los Angeles, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 109: New Orleans fur dealer discuses union charges, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 110: NLRB halts bargaining of leatherworkers union, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 111: NLRB order to rehire 8 Geraldine novelty employees...., 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 112: Nonunion bias barred in welfare benefits, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 113: Off-season wage discussion begun by Conference Group, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 114: Pay raises granted Canada fur workers in New Agreement, 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 115: Perjury charged to fur union head, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 116: Phila. Fur workers remain on job as they bargain for new contract, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 117: Pittsburgh election for fur workers set, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 118: Potash injured by stone, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 119: Proposal for arbitration under contract rejected by Assn., says union manager, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 120: Red trial delayed by Potash injury, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 121: 'Red' union barred from labor voting, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 122: Report guild, union may be near accord on new labor pact, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 123: Restore contract union asks mfrs., 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 124: Rules on sick benefit funds, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 125: Shutdown may hit fur trade next Monday, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 126: Strike called Monday, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 127: Strike hits most AFM shops, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 128: Strike talk crops up again, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 129: Strike threat looms for dressing firms, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 130: Striking glove lining workers reject offer, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 131: Stylist employees get $5 wage rise, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 132: Stylists Assn. in dispute with union over request for cost-of-living rise, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 133: Stylists-Union meet again today to talk about labor contract, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 134: Tannery work still halted in Gloversville, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 135: Texas Judge bars union, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 136: Toronto fur workers get 10% wage rise in new agreement, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 137: Toronto Union signs new wage agreement, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 138: Two Assn. members settle with union, resume work, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 139: Two union leaders before grand jury, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 140: Two-wage system reinstate in fur industry arbitration, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 141: Union aide defies house red inquiry, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 142: Union asks AFM to permit individual wage agreements, 1950-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 143: Union asks Canada to lower 25% tax, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 144: Union asks Mfrs. Assn. to call meeting on skin 'price raising', 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 145: Union asks severance pay as IJ Fox talks continue, 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 146: Union Assn., reach accord on lower pay for some lines, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 147: Union calls meeting to discuss hearings, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 148: Union claims number of individual settlements on its labor demands, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 149: Union contract talks fail, Mfrs. say..., 1948-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 150: Union disputes Greenberg on decision, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 151: Union ends strike at Va Oak Tannery, 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 152: Union group visits Washington to demand excise tax repeal, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 153: Union head urges skin price rollback to '45 levels to restore good business, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 154: Union leader lied local loses rights, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 155: Union leadership gets vote of confidence, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 156: Union letter on skin prices draws replies from dealers, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 157: Union letter request Mfrs. Committee restore contract, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 158: Union locals call meeting on foreign dressing, dyeing, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 159: Union rejects IJ Fox offer, arbitration on, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 160: Union seeks writ to bar fur lockout, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 161: Union sues Associated Mfrs. for $5,000,000 in damages, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 162: Union to attack skin prices, excise tax, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 163: Union to step up its efforts to halt contracting, says Gold, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 164: Union will strike unless mfrs. Agree to 10% raise, 37 1/2 hours, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 165: Union would stay move for injunction, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 166: Union, association working on two-price wage pattern, 1950-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 167: United Mfrs., union, ratify contract with 10% collective wage increase, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 168: Upstate Clove liners strike, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 169: Wage increase by Teetz-McKay Co., 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 170: Weigh strike at Tanneries, 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 171: Won't deal with the Union, Gloversville Tanners group states, 1948-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 172: 8,000 fur workers in walkout here, 1951-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 173: Access to NLRB denied fur union, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 174: Bay state tanners expected to strike, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 175: Decision reserved on associated plea to end union suit, 1948-1950 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 176: Deported Potash off to Poland 'Confident' he will come back, 1948-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 177: Early break now possible in fur strike, 1948-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 178: Expect end of deadlock in glove strike, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 179: Fur and leather workers' union expelled by CIO, 1948-1953 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 180: Fur strike begins Thurs. unless manufacturers yield, 1950-1952 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 181: Fur union leader assails manufacturers' testimony, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 182: Gold reelected union head, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 183: Guild settles with union on dressing.., 1949-1951 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 184: Industry distress is laid to excises, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Item 185: Labor mfr's rift continues, 1948-1949 (Box 183, Folder 1)
- Fur, Leather and Machine Workers Union, Publication (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Free Irving Potash: victim of the Smith Act, witch hunting and hysteria, 1952; Publication (Box 183, Folder 2)
    Author: Trade Union Committee to Free Irving Potash
  - Item 2: The leather workers of Fulton County: a history of struggle, 1979; Publication (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: To the Delegates of the First National Furriers Convention to establish a new Union, 1928; Publication (Box 183, Folder 2)
    Notes: Transcript
- United States. Supreme Court., Publication (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October Term, 1949 no.: in the matter of the arbitration of certain controversies between Lionel Lane, ... and Endicott Johnson Corporation: Petition for writ of certiorari to the Supreme Court of the State of, Publication (Box 183, Folder 3)
    Author: United States. Supreme Court.
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Local 64 News, 1946; Publication (Box 183, Folder 4)
    Author: Joint Board of Fur Dressers
    Notes: vol.2:no.8
  - Item 2: Local 64 News, 1948; Publication (Box 183, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-3
  - Item 3: Local 64 News, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.5:no.6
  - Item 4: Report of Exec. Bd. Committee appointed by President Murray to investigate charges against the Int'l. Fur & Leather Workers Union, 1950; Publication (Box 183, Folder 4)
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Leatherette, Publication (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Moench Tanner, 1940; Publication (Box 183, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.2:no.14
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Fur floor boys organize for jobs, peace and freedom, 1940; Publication (Box 183, Folder 6)
    Author: International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada
  - Item 2: Leather Workers News, 1947; Publication (Box 183, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1947 July. 2 copies
  - Item 3: The Time has come a personal letter to you from Richard B. O'Keefe, Int'l. Fur & Leather Workers Union, Publication (Box 183, Folder 6)
    Author: Richard B. O'Keefe
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Group Benefit Plan for Participating Member Companies, 1946; Publication (Box 183, Folder 7)
    Author: Tanners Association of Fulton County, Inc.
  - Item 2: Make certain that this form of treachery shall never endanger us again, 1947; Publication (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Statement of income and expenses, 1946; Publication (Box 183, Folder 7)
    Author: Furriers Joint Council of New York
  - Item 4: Victory will be ours, 1943; Publication (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1947; Publication (Box 183, Folder 7)
    Author: Massachusetts Leather Insurance Plan
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Analysis of Taft-Hartley Bill., Publication (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: CIO pays dividends, 1928; Publication (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: National Furriers Convention, 1928; Publication (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1944; Publication (Box 183, Folder 8)
    Author: Joint Board of Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions - IFLWU-CIO, Local 64
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A plan of group insurance, 1947; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
    Author: Luggage Workers' Health, Welfare and Insurance Fund, Local 62
  - Item 2: A plan of group insurance, 1945; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
    Author: Transylvania Tanning Co.
  - Item 3: Free Irving Potash, 1952; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Souvenir Journal..30th Jubilee Celebration (Furriers Union), 1912; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: We ask justice for our union leaders!, 1949; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1945; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
    Author: Int'l. Fur & Leather Workers Union.Local 30
  - Item 7: Your Group Insurance Plan, 1945; Publication (Box 183, Folder 9)
    Author: Int'l. Fur & Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 25th Anniversary, 1937; Publication (Box 183, Folder 10)
    Notes: Souvenir booklet
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: How shall we settle labor disputes without government intervention, 1945; Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
    Notes: Transcript. Labor-management radio forum over WEEI
  - Item 2: How to win a strike, Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Job evaluation plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Protokoll der achten convention der Int. Moebel-Arbeiter-Union., 1890; Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Resolutions adopted by the Fifth Constitutional Convention, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
    Author: United Furniture Workers of America
  - Item 6: Third Annual Report, 1947; Publication (Box 184, Folder 1)
    Author: United Furniture Workers Insurance Fund
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Liberty and 1010, 1950; Publication (Box 184, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.1:no.2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9
  - Item 2: Liberty and 1010, 1951; Publication (Box 184, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1,2
  - Item 3: Ten Ten, 1951; Publication (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Ten Ten, 1952; Publication (Box 184, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.2:no.4
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 15 basic questions and answers about the UFWA Health & Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The United Furniture Workers pension plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 3)
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Press releases, correspondence, 1947-1952 (Box 184, Folder 4)
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: When the unexpected happens, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Author: John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company.
  - Item 2: Your child grows up, 1939; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Author: Edgar A. Doll
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Author: United Furniture Workers of America.
  - Item 4: Group insurance plan, 1944; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Guarding your family's health, 1949; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Author: Smillie, Wilson G. (Wilson George), 1886-1971
  - Item 6: Home care of communicable diseases, 1947; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Keep Cool, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Notes: Booklets that are part of the Health Education Program. (cartoons)
  - Item 8: Report to the sixth constitutional convention of the United Furniture, 1950; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Summary of plan covering Hospital, Medical and Surgical expenses., 1941; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Waistlines, 1937; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Author: W. W. Bauer
  - Item 11: Checkups don't hurt, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: T.B. isn't licked yet, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: You are not a Doctor, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Your aching heart, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: 15 basic questions and answers about the UFWA Health & Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Caring for the sick in the home, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Colds make you feel awful, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Foes after forty, 1949; Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Author: United Furniture Workers of America. Local 576 (Los Angeles, Calif.)
  - Item 20: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 184, Folder 5)
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New Party gives labor a choice, 1948; Publication (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: UFWA economic report: an analysis of the furniture industry, Publication (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: UFWA Steward's manual, 1945; Publication (Box 184, Folder 6)
- UFWA (United Furniture Workers of America), Publication (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Parliamentary procedure: a handy guide, Publication (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Press releases, Publication (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: UFWA Steward's manual, 1945; Publication (Box 184, Folder 7)
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report to the National Furriers Convention for the establishment of the new union, 1928; Publication (Box 184, Folder 8)
    Author: Furriers Union. National Executive Committee
- IFLWU (International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada), Publication (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Fur Workers Voice, 1941-1942 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.1:no.3-4, 8-9
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Adult labor education in a troubled world, Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
    Author: Fannia M. Cohn
  - Item 2: Can women lead?, Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Labor's voice on unemployment, Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Method and approach in a discussion of the economics of the garment industry..., Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Philosophy of workers' education, Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprint
  - Item 6: Progressive must choose, 1948; Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Social responsibility, Publication (Box 185, Folder 1)